csgostats.gg 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy | CS:GO Stats - csgostats.gg

* ## Overview

ESL Gaming Online, Inc. and its subsidiaries (collectively, "EGO" or “CSGOSTATS.GG” or "we" or "our") respect your privacy. This privacy policy (this "Policy") informs you of our privacy practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected online and how that information is used. 

This Policy applies to all websites, servers and services owned or provided by EGO (collectively, "EGO Sites"). EGO may add new sites, domain names or services from time to time. As explained below, this Policy applies only to websites owned and services maintained by EGO and not to websites or services to which links may be provided on EGO Sites. 

BY USING THIS SITE, OR ANY PRODUCT OR SERVICE OFFERED ON THIS SITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS POLICY. 

Collection of Personal Information EGO collects personal information from users of EGO Sites in connection with the access and use of the various products and services available to you on EGO Sites. These products and services may include: (i) registration as a EGO user and/or subscribing to csgostats.gg Premium; (ii) use of the csgostats.gg Client; (iii) registration for competitions and events; (iv) registration for receipt of communications like email updates and newsletters; (v) registration for certain online community services and tools like message boards, chat rooms, forums, news groups or other community services; (vi) user surveys and polls; (vii) participation in sweepstakes, contests or promotions by sponsored by EGO or third parties; and (viii) purchasing products and services. 

  1. Types of Information Collected. EGO collects information you provide to us. This may include your name, address, ZIP code, telephone number, email address, user IDs and passwords, age and date of birth, gender, billing and transaction information, product and service preferences and contact preferences. In certain instances, you may also submit similar information about other people (such as when shipping products purchased on EGO Sites). 
  2. Automatic Data Collection. In addition to the information you provide us, EGO may also automatically collect information regarding your use of EGO Sites. Our automatic data collection may include: 
    1. Cookies, web beacons or other commonly used website analytics tools. These tools collect certain standard information that your browser sends to our website such as your browser type and language and access times. These tools may also collect information about your Internet Protocol (IP) address, clickstream behavior (i.e., the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take in connection with EGO Sites) and products and services you use.

For more information on how we use cookies, please read our Cookie Policy. 

    2. Pixel tags, web beacons or other commonly used email analytics tools. These tools may collect information when you open an email or click a link contained in an email or on EGO Sites. 
  3. Analysis functionality in the csgostats.gg Service. Certain information regarding your computer and software it contains is required for effective operation of our services. By using the csgostats.gg Service, you consent to the collection and analysis of information from your computer that EGO deems reasonably necessary to identify and analyze statistics from game files provided by you. This information collection is not strictly limited to when you are logged in to the csgostats.gg Service. Information analyzed or collected by the csgostats.gg Service is from user supplied game data files, and may include hardware, network and software identifiers; system configuration information; and game data. 

  4. Commingled Information. EGO may also collect information from commercially available sources that it deems credible. Such information may include your name, address, email address and demographic data. The information EGO collects from its commercial sources may be used along with the information EGO collects when you visit EGO Sites. For example, EGO may compare the geographic information acquired from commercial sources with your IP address to derive your general geographic area. 

  5. Community Tools. From time to time, EGO may make message boards, chat rooms, forums, news groups and other community tools available to you on EGO Sites. Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information in these public areas, your information becomes public information and can be viewed and used by EGO and others. 

  6. Purpose for data collection. Data is collected for business requirements including the provisioning of EGO services and its functions and contents, answering contact requests and communicating with users, security measures, and audience measurement and marketing.

* ## How We Use Your Personal Information

We use the personal information you provide to us (i) in the manner described in this Policy, (ii) to improve and customize this site and the products and services offered to you, and (iii) as directed by you as indicated by your use of the products and services offered on this site. For example, we may use your personal information in connection with the following: 

  1. Creation of membership accounts;
  2. Analysis of game data; 
  3. Enforce bans;
  4. Offers to participate in competitions and events;
  5. Delivery of email updates and newsletters; 
  6. Communications of offers for promotions, sweepstakes and contests; 
  7. Invitations to participate in user surveys and polls; 
  8. Execution of purchases of products and services; and
  9. Providing software updates and interactive materials.

We may also use your personal information to contact you offline concerning the products and services offered on this site. You are able to opt out of communication at any time by using the “unsubscribe” feature within the communication you receive, or by revoking consent to our services. 

* ### Sharing of Personal Information

EGO will not sell, rent or lease the personal information you provide. EGO will only share your personal information: 

  1. With entities owned or controlled by EGO; 
  2. With your consent; 
  3. With persons or entities engaged by EGO to carry out or fulfill EGO operations or business activities; 
  4. In connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets by EGO; 
  5. As required by a duly authorized request from a government authority, to comply with any law, regulation, warrant, subpoena or order from a court or governmental authority, and to help prevent or investigate suspected fraud, harassment or violation of any law, rule, regulation, EGO policy or EGO terms and conditions; and 
  6. As otherwise stated in this Policy. 

* ## Use and Disclosure of Anonymous Information

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information (i.e., generic information that does not identify you personally) when you visit any EGO Site. We may use non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of EGO Sites and to enable us to personalize the products and services offered on EGO Sites. We may also aggregate non-personally identifiable information collected in a manner which does not identify any individual. We reserve the right to use this information in any manner we deem appropriate. 

* ## Children Under 13

EGO Sites are not directed to children under the age of 13. EGO Sites prohibit registration by, and EGO will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from, anyone under the age of 13. If you believe EGO has collected personal information about your child, you may contact us at the address set forth below to request removal of such information. 

* ## California Do Not Track Disclosure

EGO does not collect personal information from users over time and across third party websites or online services. However, we work with third party partners who use unique identifiers to help us understand use of EGO Sites. The unique identifiers used by third parties on our sites may be combined with information collected about you over time and across third party websites or online services. 

* ## Links to Third Party Sites

EGO Sites may include links to third party websites or services. EGO does not control such third party sites and their privacy practices are not covered by this policy. The presence of a link on EGO Sites does not constitute an endorsement or representation regarding any third party website or service. 

* ## Information Storage and Security

The protection of your personal information is important to EGO. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure of this information, EGO utilizes appropriate physical, technical and administrative procedures to safeguard the information we collect. However, no system can ever be fully protected against every possible hazard and we cannot guarantee that communications between you and us or the information stored on EGO Sites or our servers (or those of our agents and service providers) will be completely free from unauthorized access and disclosure and your use of any EGO Site demonstrates your assumption of this risk. 

* ## Your Choices

EGO provides you with the opportunity to choose and alter your preferences regarding the communications you receive from us. You will be provided with the opportunity to indicate whether you want to receive general communications about products, services, special offers or invitations to participate in various programs. You may opt out of receiving these general communications by using one of the following methods: (i) select the email "opt out" or "unsubscribe" link, or follow the opt-out instructions included in each communication, or (ii) write to EGO at the address below. Be sure to provide your name, email and postal address, and specific relevant information about your privacy preferences. Subscription communications may include email newsletters and updates expressly requested by you. After you request such communications, you may opt out of receiving them by using one of the following methods: (i) select the email "opt out" or "unsubscribe" link, or follow the opt-out instructions included in each subscription communication, or (ii) return to the Web page(s) where you originally requested such services and follow the opt-out instructions. 

You may change or edit information you have provided as part of your user profile by logging in to your EGO account and changing the information. You may export and delete your user profile by logging into your EGO account accessing your privacy settings. You may revoke consent at any time by logging into your EGO account and accessing your privacy settings. 

* ## International Users

If you are visiting this site from a location outside the United States, your connection will be through servers located in the United States and all information you provide will be processed and maintained in our web servers and internal systems located within the United States. By using this site, you authorize the export of personal information to the United States and its storage and use as specified above. 

* ## Payment Transactions 

For a contract, in which you have to pay a fee, provided that the purchase was made via the website, your credit card information will be collected by the payment processor (credit card number, country, holder of the credit card) in accordance with Art. 6 (1) (a) and (f) GDPR credit card, credit card verification code (CVV code) and expiration date of your credit card), your name, bank account number and bank code if you choose the direct debit or if you choose another payment method or if you choose SEPA direct debit, your IBAN (international bank account number) and your BIC (International bank code of the institution of the debtor), and your home address. Please note that your credit card details or PayPal payments are collected and processed by your payment processor in relation to your payments for the service. 

* ## Social Media

EGO maintains online presence within social networks and platforms in order to communicate with customers and users active there, and to inform them about EGO services. When calling the respective networks and platforms, the terms and conditions and the data processing guidelines apply to their respective operators. 

Unless otherwise stated in our Privacy Policy, users' data will be processed as long as they communicate with EGO within social networks and platforms, e.g. write posts on EGO’s online presence or send messages. 

* ## Integration of Services and Contents of Third Parties

Based on EGO’s legitimate interests (such as interest in the analysis, optimization and economic operation of our online offer within the meaning of Art. 6 (1) lit. GDPR), EGO make use of content or services offered by third-party providers in order to provide their content and services, such as including videos (hereinafter collectively referred to as "Content").

This always presupposes that the third party providers of this content perceive the IP address of the users, since they could not send the content to their browser without the IP address. The IP address is therefore required for the presentation of this content. EGO endeavors to use only content whose respective providers use the IP address solely for the delivery of the content. Third parties may also use so-called pixel tags (invisible graphics, also referred to as "web beacons") for statistical or marketing purposes. The "pixel tags" can be used to evaluate information such as visitor traffic on the pages of this website. The pseudonymous information may also be stored in cookies on the user's device and may include, but is not limited to, technical information about the browser and operating system, referring web sites, visit time, and other information regarding the use of EGO Sites.

  1. #### YouTube

EGO embeds videos on the YouTube platform of Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA 

Privacy policy: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=de Opt-Out: https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated. 

  2. #### Facebook

EGO also use social plugins ("plugins") of the social network facebook.com, which is provided by Facebook Ireland, on the basis of EGO’s legitimate interests (analysis, optimization and economical operation of EGO’s online offer as defined in Art. 6 (1) lit. GDPR) Ltd., 4 Grand Canal Square, Grand Canal Harbor, Dublin 2, Ireland ("Facebook"). The plugins can represent interaction elements or content (such as videos, graphics or text contributions) and can be recognized by one of the Facebook logos (white "f" on blue tile, the terms "Like", "Like" or a "thumbs up" sign) or are marked with the addition "Facebook Social Plugin". The list and appearance of Facebook Social Plugins can be viewed here: https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/. 

Facebook is certified under the Privacy Shield Agreement, which provides a guarantee to comply with European privacy legislation (https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt0000000GnywAAC&status=Active). 

When a user invokes the feature that contains such a plugin, their device establishes a direct connection to the Facebook servers. The content of the plugin is transmitted by Facebook directly to the device of the user and incorporated by him into the online offer. In the process, user profiles can be created from the processed data. EGO has no control over the amount of data Facebook collects using this plugin. 

By integrating the plugins, Facebook receives the information that a user has accessed the corresponding page of the online offer. If the user is logged in to Facebook, Facebook can assign the visit to his Facebook account. If users interact with the plugins, for example, press the Like button or leave a comment, the information is transmitted from your device directly to Facebook and stored there. If a user is not a member of Facebook, there is still the possibility that Facebook will find out and save their IP address. 

The purpose and scope of the data collection and the further processing and use of the data by Facebook, as well as the related rights and setting options for the protection of your privacy, can be found in the privacy policy of Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/. 

If a user is a Facebook member and does not want Facebook to collect data about him via this online offer and link it to his member data stored on Facebook, he must log out of Facebook and delete their cookies before using EGO Sites. Other settings and inconsistencies regarding the use of data for advertising purposes are possible within the Facebook profile settings: https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads or via the USA site http://www.aboutads.info / choices / or the EU page http://www.youronlinechoices.com/. The settings are platform independent and they are adopted for all devices, such as desktop computers or mobile devices. 

  3. #### Twitter

Features of the Twitter service are included on EGO Sites (Twitter, Inc. 1355 Market St, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94103, USA). By clicking on the Twitter button and the "Re-Tweet" function, the websites you visit are linked to your Twitter account and shared with other users. This data is also transmitted to Twitter. EGO points out that as the provider of the EGO Sites, EGO is not aware of the content of the transmitted data and their use by Twitter. 

More information can be found in the privacy policy of Twitter at: https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en Opt-Out: https://twitter.com/personalization 

  4. #### Twitch TV

Twitch TV plug-ins (Twitch Interactive, Inc., 225 Bush Street, 9th Floor, San Francisco, CA 94104, USA) are integrated into EGO Sites. Privacy Policy: https://www.twitch.tv/p/legal/privacy-policy/ If you do not want Twitch to associate visiting our pages with your Twitch TV user account, please log out of your Twitch TV user account beforehand. 

  5. #### PayPal, Xsolla, and Stripe 

We make use of different payment providers. 

PayPal: 2211 North First Street San Jose, California 95131   
Privacy Policy: https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full 

Xsolla: 15260 Ventura Boulevard Suite 2230, Sherman Oaks, CA 91403,  
Tel: +1 (818) 435-6613   
Privacy Policy: https://www.xsolla.com/privacypolicy/ 

Stripe: 185 Berry Street, Suite 550, San Francisco, CA 94107   
Privacy Policy: https://stripe.com/us/privacy 

* ### Changes to this Policy

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to make changes to this Policy at any time and from time to time. EGO will undertake reasonable efforts to notify you of material changes to this Policy. We encourage you to review this Policy regularly for changes. Your continued use of EGO Sites following the posting of any changes to this Policy indicates your agreement to be bound by the terms of this Policy as revised. 

If you have any other questions, comments or complaints about this Policy, please contact us via email at privacy (at) csgostats.gg (dot) net or write to us at: 

Legal Counsel  
ESL Gaming Online, Inc.  
1212 Chestnut Street  
Burbank, California 91506  
USA 

If you have questions about data protection, you can also contact the data protection officer by email dpo@eslgaming.com
